Guide to the Washington Area Women's Center records, 1868-1989 MS2344
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Reprints, 1868, 1920, 1966-1980; 1966-1980; Series 5
  - Stern, Marjorie; An Insider's View of the Teachers' Union and Women's Rights; American Federation of Teachers, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Swidler, Leonard; Jesus Was a Feminist (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Syfers, Judy; Why I Want a Wife [also in Spanish]; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Tennov, Dorothy; Open Rapping; Reflections on Skegness Two Days Later (1971); Know, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Third World Women's Alliance; Women in the Struggle (1971); Radical Women, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Tiedt, Iris M.; Realistic Counseling for High School Girls (1972); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Tobias, Sheila; Educating Women for Leadership; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Torrey, Jane W.; Psychoanylsis: A Feminist Revision; Words That Oppress; KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Tracey, Lee; Rosa Luxemberg: Revolutionary Theoretician; News & Letters - Women's Liberation Committees, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Vanauken; Freedom for Movement Girls - Now (1969); A Primer for the Last Revolution (1968, revised 1971); Southern Student Organizing Committee; KNOW, Inc., 1968-1971; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Walker, S. Jay; Frederick Douglass and Woman Suffrage; Racism/Sexism: Theology and History, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Walstedt, Joyce Jennings; "Corporeal Orgasm* and Personality Development In the Human Male (A Spoof in the Manner of Freud); KNOW, Inc., Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Washington D.C. Women's Liberation; Towards a Radical Women's Movement (…Bob Dylan); Washington D.C. Women's Liberation, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Weathers, Diane; Is Liberation Really Good for Women? [An Interview with Phyllis Schafly] (9/18/1979); Family Circle, 1979 September 9; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Webb, Marilyn Salzman; Towards a Radical Women's Movement (1968); Washington D.C. Women's Liberation, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Weiss, Kay, M.P.H.; Contempt for Women: What Medical Students Learn in our Best Universities (April-May 1975); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Weiss, Laura B.; Women & Work; Center for Career Planning & Placement, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Weisstein, Naomi; Psychology Constructs the Female, or, The Fantasy Life of the Male Psychologist; "Woman as Nigger" (October 1969); New England Free Press, 1969 October; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Weitzman, Lenore J., Deborah Eifler, Elizabeth Hokada and Catherine Ross; Sex-Role Socialization in Picturebooks for Preschool Children (May 1972); American Journal of Sociology, 1972 May; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Wells, Audrey S.; On Dropouts, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Wells, Lyn; American Women: Their Use and Abuse (1969); Southern Student Organizing Committee; New England Free Press, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - West, Anne Grant; The Black and White of Women's Liberation (1971); Response; KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - White, Barbara Ehrlich; Women's Caucus of the College Art Association Survey of the Status of Women in 164 Art Departments in Accredited Institutions of higher Education: Statistical Analysis of Survey Data (1973); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - White, Martha S.; Psychological and Social Barriers to Women in Science (October 1970); KNOW, Inc., 1970 October; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Whitlock, Kay and Robin Smith; De-Mystifying "The Lavender Menace": A N.O.W. Primer on Lesbian-Baiting (April 1977); NOW Task Force on Sexuality & Lesbianism, April 1977, 1977 April; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Widmer, Kingsley; Reflections of a Male Housewife: On Being a Feminist Fellow-Traveller (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Will, Shirley Hill; Native Women Today: Sexism and the Indian Woman; Racism/Sexism: Theology and History, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Williams, Susan; In Defense of Marxist Feminism: A Critique of Current Trends in the Socialist Feminist Movement; Lesbianism: A Socialist Feminist Perspective; Women: Revolutionary Vanguard of the Working Class A Marxist Critique of Current Trands in theSocialist Feminist Movement; Women's Psychology: Mental Illness as a Social Disease; Radical Women, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Willis, Ellen; 'Consumerism' and Women; Women's Liberation, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Windoffer, Melba; Women Who Work; Radical Women, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Winkler, Ilene; Women Workers: The Forgotten Third of the Working Class; International Socialists, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Wittman, Carl; A Gay Manifesto; Radical Education Project, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Wolfson, Alice; Women and Health; D.C. Women's Liberation, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Wolfson, Sharon; 12 Years Old and Turned On, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Women's Liberation; The Politics of 'Free' Love: Forced Fornication (1969); Women's Liberation, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Women's Liberation Movement within the Youth International Party (YIP); An Exegesis on Women's Liberation; Women's Liberation/YIPPIE, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Wood, Myrna; We May Not Have Much But There's a Lot of Us!; Radical Education Project, Undated; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Wood, Sally Medora; Questions I Should Have Answered Better: A Guide to Women Who Dare to Speak Publicly (1971); KNOW, Inc., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Wortis, Sheli; Child-Rearing and Women's Liberation (1970); Boston Area Child Care Action Group, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Wyckoff, Hogie; Problem Solving Groups for Women (Winter 1973); Issues in Radical Therapy, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - Wynn, Karen; Second Thoughts About Sterilization (1977); SISTER, Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - Zetkin, Clara; Conversations Between [by Clara Zetkin, 1920, included in Clara Zetkin's pamphlet "Lenin on the Woman Question"], Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 74)
- Audiotapes, 1972-1975; Series 6
  Arranged in no particular order.
  This series contains audio recordings that cover the date range 1972-1975.
  - Feminist Radio Network, CART FRN 01 May 1975, typed & handwritten note FRN details programming on tape, WGTB, 1975 May 1; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder folder #)
    5" reel donor note: Audiotape
  - No tape number. Feminist Radio Network. Violence Against Women, reel 5. Harper - Freeway. Phantom Comm. Safety Tips. Sue Self-Defense. Reel #5, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 1)
  - Prime Time air check, 60 min. sony cassette, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 2)
    cassette donor note: Audiotape
  - Demo Radio Free Women - Toronto. 5 min. & 12 sec., undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 3)
  - No tape number, no box top. Washinton Area Feminist Theatre, 5-27-1973., 1973 May 27; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 4)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape
  - No tape number. Feminist Radio Network. Feminist Alliance Against Rape. 12-14-1974, 1974 December 14; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 5)
  - Radio Free Women. Open Marriage and Memoirs of an Ex-Prom Queen. Penny Addis, Barbara Finness, Sara Reitz. 8-2-1972, 1972 August 2; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 6)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape 42
  - Back of box states: America 73, Women's Lib Arena ERA, 2-25-1973. Reel 2 of 2., 1973 February 25; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 7)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape 43
  - Margie Cart. Limbo. Mumbo Jumbo Tender Lady (song titles - probably Margie Adam), undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 8)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape 44
  - Radio Free Women, Washington, D.C. Politics of Rape. Billie Malkin and Karen Kollias, D.C. Rape Crisis Center. 7-19-1972, 1972 July 19; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 9)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape 53
  - Radio Free Women, Washington, D.C. Interview with Diane Sward, a rock music manager….[more on box] 12-18-1973 [or 1974?], Circa 1973 December 18; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 10)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T67a
  - Radio Free Women, Washington, D.C. Interview with Leslie Jacobson, author of "The Amateur: Reflections on Zelda"… [more on box] 6-2-1974, 1974 June 2; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 11)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T70
  - Radio Free Women, Philadelphia, WUHY [correct letters of station?] Woman and Law. Nov. 1974, 1974 November; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 12)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T90
  - Radio Free Women, Philadelphia. Women in Sweden. (box also states "Mining Music"), undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 13)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T92
  - Child Sexual Assault. On tape: "Childhood Sexual Abuse Safety." [might need to be restricted], undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 14)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T111a
  - Child Sexual Assault #2. Barb Myers on tape #2 [might need to be restricted], undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 15)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T111b
  - Lee Brown #2, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 16)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T114b
  - Radio Free Women, bloopers, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 17)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T121
  - Feminist Radio Network. Mother's Day. Interview with the mothers of four Feminist Radio members., undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 18)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T125
  - Women in Denmark, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 19)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T136
  - Chris - Sophie's. Tape 2, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 20)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T147
  - Class and the Family. Health #1, Skilled Labor, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 21)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T148
  - New music. 1 hell, 1 shitwork. Waitresses "full track dub", undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 22)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T150
  - Jill Raymond #1, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 23)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T170a
  - Jill Raymond #2, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 24)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T170b
  - Grand Jury Project, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 25)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T171a
  - Emmy. G-J intro, narrative, heads, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 26)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T171b
  - Radio Free People. Conference: Women Give the Media Their Message. Priscilla Toumey, Grace Glueck, and Kitty Krupat, NYU, Dec 7, 1974, unedited. 3 pages detailed typed info inside box., 1974 December 7; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 27)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T172a
  - "Women Give the Media Their Message", reel 2. Ruth Shereff, NYU, July 1974. Discussion from the floor., 1974 July; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 28)
    7" reel donor note: Audiotape T172b
  - tape #10, half blank. Raleigh Inn Waitress + Manager, waitress #1, waitress tape #1, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 29)
    5" reel donor note: Audiotape T184
  - Chris' Mom; edited Marg. Murphey, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 30)
    5" reel donor note: Audiotape T189
  - Meg Christian, side 1 & 2, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 31)
    5" reel donor note: Audiotape T190
  - Sophie's 4 15-Dec-??, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 32)
    5" reel donor note: Audiotape T191
  - About Halloween, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 33)
    donor note: Audiotape T192
  - Sherl's Mom, undated; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 34)
    5" reel donor note: Audiotape T196
  - Feminist Radio Network. Violence Against Women teach-in. Reel #1. MLK Library 1-18-1975. Sherri Myers - culture., 1975 January 18; Series 6 (Box 35, Folder reel 35)
    5" reel donor note: Audiotape T213
- T-shirts, undated; Series 7
  - [no text, image of diverse women's faces emerging from globe into sun rays], undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 1)
  - 5th National Women's Music Festival, undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 2)
  - Anonymous Was a Woman, undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 3)
  - CLF - 80 9 (iris inside woman's symbol), undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 4)
  - Equality of Rights Under the Law [ERA], undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 5)
  - Ladies' Sewing Circle and Terrorist Society 1977, undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 6)
  - Lammas (3 women's symbols interlocking), undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 7)
  - LGT Pride 1981 Atlanta (OUT pink triangle), undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 8)
  - Michigan Womyns Festival (piano with trees), undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 9)
  - National March on Washington for Lesbian & Gay Rights STAFF 1987, undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 10)
  - National Womens' Film Circuit, Moonforce Media, undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 11)
  - New Victoria Printers, Inc., undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 12)
  - Pride 1982 Staff, Washington, D.C., undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 13)
  - Roanoke Valley Women's Retreat 1981, undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 14)
  - Roanoke Valley Women's Retreat 1982, undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 15)
  - Stonewall Then Atlanta Now! LGT Pride 1982 (apple turns into peach), undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 16)
  - Strittmater Lives, undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 17)
  - University of Maryland Women's Center, undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 18)
  - Washington Area Women's Center/ Full Moon Cruise/ 1980, undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 19)
  - Woman Hag Crone Witch Spinster (Amazon warrior with 2 lamma weapons), undated; Series 7 (Box 36, Item 20)
- Graphics, 1973-1982; Series 8
  Arranged in the original order.
  This series contains posters and photographs primarily oversize materials and covers the date range 1973-1982.
  - Rising Women Coffeehouse Bookshop. "…and more in 1975". Meg Christian; Hysteria, D.C.'s own Women's Dance Band; "1976 - finally, the coffeehouse." 4 flyers., 1975-1976; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 6)
  - Rising Women Coffeehouse Collective. 1975 - the beginning, New Haven Women's Liberation Band. Women's Dance Benefit for Women's Coffeehouse Bookshop. On Tour: Berkeley Women's Music Collective; Women Make Movies. Double Women's Concert: Moonshine Jug Band and Wine, Women and Song., Series 8 (Oversize-folder 7)
  - Rising Women Coffeehouse Collective. 1976. Very large blue & white posterboard with many b&w photos of performers. Photos by Barton Rising Women's Coffeehouse, "1974-78 in D.C.", 1974-1978; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 8)
  - Rising Women Coffeehouse Collective. November 1976 Closing flyer. June 24th, 1977 Tonight., 1976-1977; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 9)
  - Rising Women Coffeehouse. If you missed this, and even if you didn't, another cruise is September 2nd., Undated; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 10)
  - Rising Women Coffeehouse. Small image of Kay Gardner concert on larger white posterboard. "We lost money on this, but it was nice!", Undated; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - AMERICA. "When will the ignorance end?" 3rd World Gay Conference, Washington, D.C., October 12-15, 1979. Unknown artist, silkscreen., Series 8 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Celebrate Women's Week! Feb.22 to 27. Trinity College. Judy Reagan was one of the performers. On white paper board. [Year was 1982.], Series 8 (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Celebration 82! An Evening of Women's Performers, Saturday, Feb. 27th, 1982. Trinity College. Performers include Ladderinth, Judy Reagan and Susan Abod. On white paper board., Series 8 (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Child of Myself. Poem by Pat Parker. [no date]. [Book cover illustration?], Undated; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 6)
  - Female nude by unknown artist. possibly charcoal. [no date]., Undated; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 6)
  - History of Working Women, All Soul's Church, Friday, June 25 [circa 1971]. "Women's History told in slides." With speakers Bessie Lou Cornett and music by Bev Grant and Lucha. [unknown artist of poster]. Very large poster., Series 8 (Oversize-folder 4)
  - Lesbian Heritage/D.C. Black and silver large poster on board. Artist is Sudie Rakusin, 1980., Series 8 (Oversize-folder 5)
  - Lunatics Calendar 1980. Cover + 7 sheets. [graphics]., Series 8 (Oversize-folder 6)
  - Second Annual Women's Film Festival, Women Make Movies II, American Film Institute, Sept. 8-24, 1981. Offset., Series 8 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Women & the Draft. "Women are Invited to Discuss the Issue of Women & the Draft". George Washington University, March 1st, 1980. Wendy Stevens, possibly the artist. Large white posterboard., Series 8 (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Women in Gear, Fran Lynch black and white photo. 1979., Series 8 (Oversize-folder 4)
  - Women's Coffehouse/Bookstore of Washington. [from off our backs, February 1975]., 1975 February; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 5)
  - Women's Nite Out Extravaganza! 10/21/78. Benefit for WAWC, All Soul's Church. Performers include Dorthoy Allison, Wendy Stevens, Judy Reagan. Two copies of orange poster. On back of one are 2 bumper stickers: "Sisterhood is Powerful" and "Sisterhood Feels Good"., 1978 October 21; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 11)
  - "Collective Consciousness". Baltimore, GCCB, March 6-7, 13,14. [On back: 82-0060.], Undated; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 5)
  - "Eye to Eye" sales, $8. Folder board., Undated; Series 8 (Box 37)
  - "Feminist + Humorist =FUMERIST." Kate Clinton Making Light. Bread & Roses Coffeehouse, Feb 6 [no year]. Also: Judy Reagan plus Tukie Requa. Sponsored by Muses Collective., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - "I Like to Think of Harriet Tubman." Poem by Susan Griffin. On back: 82-0056., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - "Premonitions of Crytal Night," poem by Judith Malina, Oct. 22, 1973. Poster by Come! Unity Press. Gold background. Labeled on back "82-0054"., 1973 October 22; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - "Remember the Future." Black and white photos of five female nudes in a landscape. Photo by Nina Sabaroff. On back: 82-0062., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - "Washington Area Women Are Centered. Buy a shirt for yourself or a friend." Red poster, silkscreen., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - 15 Color photographs of National Association of Women's Centers Conference., Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - A March to Stop Violence Against Women. Saturday night, April 29, 1978. Small orange poster., 1978 April 29; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Beth Karbe, black and white nude photo, self-portrait. "BCK 1978" below photo on board., Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Black and white photo of WAWC informational table with two members in front of banner. [On back: photo by Peggy, 82-0018.], Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Black and white photo of woman, possibly holding a guitar. Print #7-10, BCK 78. [On back: Susan Erickson.], Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Black and white photo within a white frame mat of group of women outdoors, rasising hands., Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Black and white photograh of large group of women around conference table, possibly D.C. Area Feminist Alliance. [On back: JEB (Joan E. Biren) photographer.], Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Cheryl Lees black and white portrait photogragh. BCK 1979 on front. [BCK is Beth Karbe, also a WAWC member.], Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Collective visions. National Poster Art. June 19th to September 7th. Local 1734 Art Gallery. Orange poster. On back: stamped "Community Educational Exhibition, Local 1734.", Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Color photograph portrait of Elaine Nobel. [On back: "Elaine Nobel spoke at Georgetown University, 2/78.], 1978; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Cris Williamson & Trete Fure, with Cam Davis and Carrie Barton. April 21, 1974. Roanoke College. First Friday Productions., 1974 April 21; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Cruise tickets, June 29. [no year.] Annapolis Harbor. Handwritten poster., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Folder with "Feminist Expressions" items copyright Carrera-Black, 1977. Title page plus 23 color pages of pasted down greeting cards (pen and ink drawings of women by Lauren Weil or Sudie Rakusin; some pages are numbered at bottom right corner) plus 11 floating greeting cards, numbers 82-0003A, B, D, E, G, I, K, L, N, O, Q. All in archival bag., Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Invitation to "Lesbian Faces/Lesbian Words," exhibit June 7, 1981, in D.C. Women's Center. "Photos by Beth Karbe." [Black and white photo on other side is probably Beth Karbe in femme drag and Sudie Rakusin in butch drag.], 1981 June 7; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Lesbian/Gay Arts Festival, Gay Community Center. Friday, Saturday, Sunday. Performers include Judy Reagan and D.C.'s Different Drummers. White poster. [circa unknown.], Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Margie Adam Concert April 7, Lisner Aud. [no year]. Poster., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Mary Watkins Trio, special appearance by Michell Parkerson. Oct. 10 [no year]., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Maxine Feldman concert poster. 1977 or 1978. St. Mark's Church. [First DC concert. Poster artist unknown.], 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Meg Christian with Diane Lindsay. April 27, 1987, Roanoke College. First Friday Productions., 1983 April 23; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - National Gay Task Force, Rhose Island Affiliate. Mockup for poster., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - National Women's Independence Day Celebration, sponsored by the Congressional Union. July 4th [c. 1978]. "Relighting Feminist Fires." Bella Abzug, Robin Morgan, Gloria Steinem and many others. Poster., 1978 July 4; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Negative of five women, four seated with one standing. It has been masked to show four women, three seated and one standing. [Mask note says: "Work print, mailing out the Furies."], Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Poetry reading, November 12th. Includes Andrea Wyatt, Joanne Jimason, Margie Sadin. Second Story Books, Beneift for Women's Pentagon Action, 1980. On back: "if you need more, let me know.", Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Rita Mae Brown, large portrait shot, black and white photo., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Sign. Poem by Melanie Kaye, 1977. Graphic by Paula King. Rape Relief Hotline. On paperboard., Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Small black and white photo of four women, outdoor scene. [On back of photo is "B".], Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Susan Saxe "Support, Protect Our Sisters and Brothers Underground." By artist Peg Averill. [On back: 82-0051.] Posterground., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Sweet Honey in the Rock, 7 Years Together. All Souls Church, Nov. 7 & 8 [no year]. On back: 82-0058., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - The Flight of Phoenix, A Band of Women. "Women Celebrating Women" dance, 1979 at George Washington University., Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - The Pleasure Chest, a toy store for sophicated adults. On back: "uncategorized.", Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Three color photographs of "Sappho Café" given with handwritten note by Terre Poppe to WAWC Archives. [On back of photo: 4/7/82.] These are in a Kodak photo wallet holder., Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Three original art works by Lauren Weil, 1977. Two female figures drawn in pastel and five female figures in pencil., Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Three print graphics by Laurie White. "'Celebrate Lesbian Culture', 'Medusa Graphix,' and 'Ragings of the Medium…'". San Francisco. [no date]., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Thursday night music. April 14, 21, 28. Andrea Floyd, Tiik, Hysteria. Club Madame. [no year] paper poster., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 25)